[{"answer": "What", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "A cell phone. There was an old cell phone in the coffin", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "A cell phone. There was an old cell phone in the coffin", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes. No. It's not mine, but yes, I'm calling from a cell phone", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "There was a cell phone in the coffin when you climbed in", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "How did you end up in the coffin, sir", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Do you know your location, sir", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "American can breathe no breathe", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Get out", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "No, I can't breathe. Please get me out of here", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yes, please get me out. Help me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I have two my friend, sir. One on Federal Road and one on that place", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "that place Avenue...I think. Yeah. Shit, I don't know. Just give me that one", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yes, that place", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend, I need to talk to my friend. It's an absolute emergency. Have her call me. Use star sixt", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I just have a few questions for you, Mister my friend", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "It's important that I get this information. It will make a rescu", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, since you know what the hell is going on, what have you done to get me out of here", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "So, that's it? I'm just supposed to rot in here because there's little you can do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It will only complicate things further and threaten your chances of rescue. my friend doesn't buy it", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, I'm covering yours. Everyone who needs to know about this does", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Two hour, six minute. my friend looks at his watch. Indeed, he has but two hours and six minutes until the time reaches 9pm", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You talk to embassy? They give money", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You talk to embassy? They give money", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No pay", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "No. They said that they don't negotiate with terrorists", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yes. You are terrorist, you son of a bitch", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Terrorists? I am terrorist", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You are terrified, so I am terrorist", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You are terrified, so I am terrorist", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Ever do", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Stop! Just please, stop! I'm just a guy. I'm just a truck driver. Okay? I'm nobody that makes decisions about anything. I just want to go home. Silence from the other end of the phone for an extended period of time", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yes. Please. Get me out of here and I'll make the video", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You make video, ransom video. This surprisingly comes as good news to my friend", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No. You make video now", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "About three weeks ago. my friend writes", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I remember all their names", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Who are you", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Let her go. Please. Please don't hurt her. The Woman is heard in the background of my friend's phone, crying muffled words through her muzzled mouth", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "No! No, please no shoot. No shoot her", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I will, I promise. Just don't shoot her. She's a mother, she's got two kids", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yes. She has two kids", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What is? What are you talking about", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "All of what", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "What do you know", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I know you're upset. And, from what I've been told, steps are being taken to get you out of there. So, hopefully it won't be much longer", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yes, thank God", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I have your official date of hire as January 4th, 2005. Is that correct", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "January 4th, 2005. Is that correct", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Given that you were alive up until the time of your termination", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Do you understand everything", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "They're dead", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I just do", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Where is money", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "What don't know", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "I don't know where the money is", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Liar", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Swear", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Yes! my friend puts the batteries back inside the flashlight. Begins screwing on the cap", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "No", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "I just saw the news. What...oh my God, baby. The flashlight dims. my friend shakes it, regaining a bit of its strength", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I missed all your calls. I left my cell phone at home. I just found out what was going on", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "The people", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Call me right away", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Call me right away", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "I love you. Swear it again", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Move! Move! Let's go", "docId": "Buried.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "my friend? my friend", "qsentId": 74}]